# JASON SILVIA

## CONTENT DEVELOPER & CONSULTANT

linkedin.com/in/jasonsilvia 401-451-6186 jgsilvia11@gmail.com

#### SUMMARY

Multi-disciplined creative professional with 10 years experience and a passion for both tech and the arts. Seeking to utilize my skills and experience in content consulting, technical analysis, training enablement, project management, and copywriting in the fields of marketing & advertisting.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Content Developer & Consultant**

Dec, 2020 - Present

- Founded The Creative Capital Show podcast.
  - Duties include recording, editing, social media, and podcast consulting for other businesses
- Providing design and content consulting services for businesses.
  - Provided consulting and design services to BAS PVD for "A Place With No Name" chef pop-up event series within The Dean Hotel. This project resulted in BAS PVD taking over The Dean Hotel's dining space.

## Marketing Content Developer | Outco

Jul, 2022 - Nov, 2022

- Analyzed current marketing content as wall as content of competitors, created new video content.
- Advised CEO on strategies to repurpose existing training assets as marketing content.

### **Content Consultant | Dell Technologies**

Nov, 2019 - Dec, 2020

- Analyzed, curated, and created training modules for multiple divisions.
- Advised leadership on production strategies which led to frequent updating of outdated content.
- Managed content schedules for both in-person & virtual new hire training events as well as tech-talks.

## Solutions Arechitect | Dell Technologies

Jun 2017 - Nov 2019

- Designed technology solutions for sales campaigns, created materials and live demos for customers.
- Created training materials that would be utilized as core curriculum for Solutions Architects.
- Became Solutions Architect bootcamp training instructor, received highest rated training by bootcamp students.

## **Email Retention Marketing Specialist | Schneider Electric**

Jun, 2012 - Dec, 2013

- Global admin for email creation/analysis tools Responsys and Litmus
- · Managed "Contractor's Newsletter" email campaign which went from worst to best performing email campaign of 2012.

## EDUCATION

New England Institute of Technology | East Greenwich, RI

2008 - 2011

Bachelor of Science - IT Networking

Full Sail University | Winter Park, FL

2004 - 2005